<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ScrollView</string>
    <string name="article_title">Life</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle"><b> It is a Precious Gift </b> </string>
    <string name="article_text">
        Life is a precious gift. It must be handled with care. We must be thankful to God for sending us on Earth and giving us such beautiful surroundings to live in.
        We must also be thankful to God for making us physically and mentally fit to live a wholesome life. Not just human beings, the life of animals,
        birds and plants is equally precious and we must value it too.
        https://in.pinterest.com/pin/288230444893497002/
        \n
        \n

        We must appreciate the good in our life and express gratitude for the same. Many people are not happy with the way things go on in their life. They criticize almost
        everything and everyone around and develop a negative outlook. They need to understand that the fact that they have been given a life to live is in itself a big thing.\n
        \n

        The fact that they are in good health is a reason to be thankful for. The fact that they are able and can work hard and make their life better is another reason to be
        grateful. They must appreciate what they have and be thankful for it. Everything else can be achieved with some effort. \n
        \n

        Many people indulge in bad habits such as smoking, drinking and taking drugs. The havoc created post consuming these can be a threat to their life as well as the life of
        those around them. Many people drink and run over their car on innocent people killing them or injuring them badly. They even hurt themselves during such incidents. Besides,
        all these things have a negative impact on a person’s health. \n
        \n

        They incur serious health problems over the time thus ruining their lives as well as the lives of their family members. They must understand that life is precious. We can
        lead a purposeful life and add value to it or waste it and end up in a mess. Many people realize this much later in life mostly after incurring a major problem. It is too late
        then and they cannot go back and relive their life properly. We must value this gift called life when there is still time and tread the right path to enjoy it. \n
        \n

        God has given us a chance to live and enjoy the beauty of the nature. Life is a precious gift and we must all value it. We must express gratitude and stay positive to make the most
        of this gift given to us. We must also value the lives of those around us.
        \n
        \n

        <b> <i> KEEP SMILING :) </i> </b>

    </string>
</resources>